{
  "title": "test",
  "description": "yesss/nooo",
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "yes",
      "back": "no"
    },
    {
      "front": "yess",
      "back": "nooo"
    },
    {
      "front": "1",
      "back": "2"
    },
    {
      "front": "3",
      "back": "4"
    },
    {
      "front": "5",
      "back": "6"
    },
    {
      "front": "7",
      "back": "8"
    },
    {
      "front": "9",
      "back": "10"
    },
    {
      "front": "11",
      "back": "12"
    },
    {
      "front": "13",
      "back": "14"
    },
    {
      "front": "15",
      "back": "16"
    },
    {
      "front": "17",
      "back": "18"
    },
    {
      "front": "19",
      "back": "20"
    },
    {
      "front": "21",
      "back": "22"
    },
    {
      "front": "23",
      "back": "24"
    }
  ]
}